O.k.
What we're doing as we have our piece of paper in front of us and we're going down that outline and we're writing our thoughts is we are trying to look for holes in the other person's case or theory, if you will.
Where are the mistakes that they made in their presentation?
So we're going to do an analysis of their evidence and their arguments.
And of course what their arguments are, are things like "Well, it?s cruel to take animals to the slaughter house." That would be an argument.
"Abortion is wrong." Ten year track appointments for professors are a good thing or a bad thing. Whatever it is. What are their arguments?
We're going to make an analysis of those and then we're also going to need to take a look at their evidence.
And their evidence are the things that they have found in research that prove these arguments to be true, or support these arguments.
So those are the two things that we're going to take a look at to try to refute the persuasive claim.
Let's look at evidence first.